Jessica Ann LaPage

Summary

Highly motivated and reliable individual with experience in event planning and coordination. Proven ability to work independently, multi-task, and delegate responsibilities. Exceptional organizational and problem solving skills.

Proficiencies

- -Planning and execution of events
- -Organization and problem solving
- -Ability to communicate with a diverse population
- -Working with multiple deadlines
- -Motivated self-starter

Work Experience

PCA Muriel LaPage	05/2009 - 06/2019
Associate Target, Hudson, WI	10/2013 - 01/2014
Sales Associate LUSH, Bloomington, MN	10/2010 - 01/2011
Tax Processor McGladrey LLP, Minneapolis, MN	02/2009 - 04/2009
Producer/ Board Operator WFMP, St. Paul, MN	05/2008 - 06/2009
Production Intern KSTP-FM, St. Paul, MN	10/2007 - 12/2007
Operations Assistant – Cosmetics Merchandising Assistant Bloomingdale's, Bloomington, MN	10/2002 - 5/2005
Radio Announcer / On Air Personality Bick Broadcasting, Sedalia, MO	10/2001 – 9/2002

Education

Associa	ate	of.	Applie	ed S	Science	e I	Degree in Radio	Broadcasting
_	_			-		_		

03/2008

Brown College, Mendota Heights, MN